Excuse the gloom,
but none may know of this meeting.
The nature of my trouble is darker still.
Over a year ago, King Lysandus of Daggerfall
died honorably on the field of battle.
He was as loyal a subject,
ally and friend... as you are.
I did grieve for him,
But his spirit does not rest.
With the spectral army, he haunts his former kingdom,
crying for revenge!
I do not know why a good and loyal man would be so cursed.
Perhaps you can find the answer
and close the marble jaws of Oblivion,
bringing peace to his soul.
I ask this as your Emperor
and as your friend.
I have one lesser request.
Several years ago, I wrote a letter
to the Queen of Daggerfall.
It never arrived.
The letter was of a sentimental and...
personal nature.
If you find and destroy that letter,
I will be grateful.
Now my champion,
rest well this night,
for tomorrow you sail for the Kingdom
of Daggerfall !